// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is 24 + 5?",
    answer: "29",
    options: [
      "32",
      "29",
      "28",
      "24"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Whats 2(2+5)",
    answer: "14",
    options: [
      "17",
      "29",
      "10",
      "14"
    ]
  },
    
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A - 1 = 7; What is A?",
    answer: "A = 8",
    options: [
      "A = 8",
      "A = 6",
      "A = 7",
      "A = 10"
    ]
  },
    
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "B + 2 = 12; What is B?",
    answer: "B = 10",
    options: [
      "B = 12",
      "B = 10",
      "B = 18",
      "B = 17"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "D + 9 = 12; What is D?",
    answer: "D = 3",
    options: [
      "D = 2",
      "D = 3",
      "D = 10",
      "D = 16"
    ]
  },
 
{

    numb: 6,
    question: "2z+3=9; what's z? ",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "3",
      "4",
      "8",
      "11"
    ]
  },



{

    numb: 7,
    question: "3m+2=8; what's m? ",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "6",
      "9",
      "2",
      "4"
    ]
  },

{

    numb: 8,
    question: "2z+2=8; what's z?",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "3",
      "6",
      "9",
      "4"
    ]
  },








{
    numb: 9,
    question: "2a+3=7; what's a? ",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "6",
      "2",
      "1",
      "9"
    ]
  },

{
    numb: 10,
    question: "2+2y=6; what's y? ",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "5",
      "2",
      "7",
      "3"
    ]
  },



{

    numb: 11,

    question: "2+3b=11; what's b? ",

    answer: "3",

    options: [

      "6",

      "3",

      "7",

      "2"

    ]

  },








{

    numb: 12,

    question: "48-7w=6; what's w? ",

    answer: "6",

    options: [

      "4",

      "9",

      "6",

      "7"

    ]

  },



{

    numb: 13,

    question: "70-8z=6; what's z? ",

    answer: "8",

    options: [

      "8",

      "5",

      "3",

      "9"

    ]

  },



{

    numb: 14,

    question: "7=2z+3; what's z?",

    answer: "2",

    options: [

      "5",

      "3",

      "2",

      "7"

    ]

  },








{
    numb: 15,
    question: "8=14-2a; what's a?",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "6",
      "1",
      "5",
      "3"
    ]
  },


 {   
    numb: 16,
    question: "3a+2=8 ; What’s a?",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "5",
      "-4"
    ]
  },

    {
     numb: 17,
    question: " 5z−3=17 ; What’s z?",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "-5",
      "1",
      "4",
      "7"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 18,
    question: " 3+2m=7 ; What’s m?",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "2",
      "5",
      "1",
      "-8"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 19,
    question: " 4+2d=14 ; What’s d? ",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "5",
      "-3",
      "-2",
      "5"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 20,
    question: "7a + 9 = 16; whats a?",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "9",
      "5",
      "1",
      "2"
    ]
  },
  
];